Ami Kevadiya Frontend web developer

■ amikevadiya05@gmail.com

+61 455332531

Sydney, Australia

Profile

I'm a creative Front End Developer with over 4.5+ years of experience designing and managing responsive websites. HTML, CSS, JQuery, Javascript, Shopify, GravCMS, and WordPress are among my abilities. React js and React Native are two languages I learn. In addition, I have over a year of expertise in Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, Figma, and XD.

Professional Experience

Sr Frontend Developer

Apr 2022 - Jan 2023

NEXTNOUS Surat, India

- Created a responsive and adaptive website with HTML5 and CSS3.
- Handle numerous design projects at once and deliver to a high quality.
- Build a website with the Bootstrap framework.
- Added a new feature in websites for better user experience
- Created and maintained HTML standard for websites.
- Redesigned website with clean, efficient coding that is responsive and user-friendly.
- · Created and managed a WordPress website.
- Solid understanding of web design principles.
- Expertise in wireframing, UX/UI design, and prototyping across various devices.
- Design an application logo and banner.
- Designed the user interface for a mobile application in Figma.

Frontend web developer

Apr 2021 - Mar 2022

Dynamic Dreamz

Surat, India

- I worked on a Shopify ecommerce store.
- I'm working on fixing the jQuery problem on Shopify.

- · Added a new feature in shopify store for better user experience.
- Create a website using the Bootstrap framework.
- · I made an animation using custom jQuery.
- Converted PSD, XD and Figma files to HTML, CSS and jQuery.
- · Converted Figma file to Shopify store.
- Work on numerous projects at the same time, prioritizing activities and ensuring that all projects are completed on schedule.
- Designed responsive and adaptive websites using HTML5 and CSS3.
- To organize work into boards, I used project management software like Jira and Trello.

Frontend web developer

Apr 2019 - Mar 2021

Casepoint Pvt.Ltd.

Surat, India

- · We were working on an eDiscovery product.
- I'm familiar with agile scrum and team foundation server (TFS).
- I worked on the Kendo UI library.
- · Worked on 508 compliance for eDiscovery product
- I primarily worked on jQuery for 508 compliance.
- I collaborated with the team to include 508 compliance into the product.
- I created a dynamic website with Grav CMS.

Web Designer

May 2018 - Apr 2019

Ecreate Infotech

Surat, India

- Designed and developed responsive and adaptive website using HTML5 and CSS3.
- Design, develop, test and deploy design feature in timely manner.
- Build a website with clean and efficient code that is responsive and accessible on all devices, platforms, and is user-friendly.
- · Added new feature in website for better user experience.
- · Created and maintained HTML standard for website.
- · Build a website with the Bootstrap framework.
- Created and managed a WordPress website.
- Worked on ACF field plugin on WordPress.
- Using wow.js, I added animation to the webpage.
- Redesigned website with clean, efficient coding that is responsive and user-friendly.
- Design an application logo and banner.
- Designed the user interface for a mobile application in Photoshop.

Skills

HTML

· CSS

JavaScript

jquery

Bootstrap

WordPress

Shopify

Gravems

Kendo UI

• 508 Compliance

Adobe Photoshop

Illustrator

XD

• Figma

React

Education

Master of computer application

Suresh Gyan Vihar University

Jun 2018 – Apr 2020

Jaipur, India

Bachelors in Computer Application

Sutex Bank College of Computer Applications & Science

Jun 2015 – Mar 2018 Surat, India

Reference

Available upon Request.